mobileorchard.com 2015-06-27

# Privacy Policy - What's On Iphone

**Privacy Policy** ****

This privacy statement covers all websites of [Dreamattic S.A.](http://www.dreamattic.com/) (“Dreamattic”). At Dreamattic, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit websites and services (“Services”) published by Dreamattic and how we safeguard your information. Please read this statement carefully before proceeding to access our **** sites. **By using the Services you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.**

**We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

**Information we collect** ****

Dreamattic is the sole owner of the information collected on its websites. Dreamattic may collect information from our users at several different points:

  * **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

Dreamattic’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use the website.

  * **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences.

We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on one of Dreamattic sites, users will not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while logging to services or programs. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains a username and encrypted password. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Comments**

Dreamattic allows readers to post comments to our online content. Under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, comments are the sole responsibility of the individual commenters. Dreamattic reserves the right to delete any comments that include hate speech, libel, plagiarism, threats, personal attacks or off-topic assertions, and inappropriate language in order to protect the integrity of the site and its users. We do not edit comments for content.   ****

**Third party links  **

Dreamattic sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Dreamattic is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Dreamattic.

**Third Party Advertising** **and Cookies** ****

Some of our third party advertising partners may distribute cookies to users in advertisements that are provided to us. Dreamattic has no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. These advertisers may be engaging in online behavioral advertising as defined by the Digital Advertising Alliance and FTC. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Dreamattic and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Mailing List**  
Dreamattic may launch a mailing list for some or all of its sites. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Dreamattic goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Dreamattic may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of our sites.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Dreamattic changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.dreamattic.com/forms/contactus).
